Mom, did you leave the gas on in the kitchen?
Yes, I can smell the smell too.  I have
put oil in the pan to heat it.
Bani, come to the kitchen to see.
Mom, the gas was out.
Hey, quickly open the kitchen window.
Go and speak.
Hey, I lit the gas, how did it go off on its own
?  The whole house would have caught fire any moment.   Okay, no problem,
you go, I will make it.
By turning the auto round.  [MUSIC]
Round by doing the auto.  Whistle and say.   There is
no water coming now, nor is there a smell of gas.
Wait, don't burn it yet.  Let me go out first.
Come on, why should I die alone?
What about the egg [music]?
Hey what is it?  Scared me.   Hey, he'll be a
coward.  [Music]
No one knows what their future will hold.
What is the matter?  I have made pakodas today.
Papa, you know the house was going to catch fire today.  I
know nothing remains in your stomach.
Yes, Papa's pet